# DeQuandelyn " Dee " Green

Dallas, TX 75238 dee469567@hotmail.com 4696858844

A motivated driven medical professional offering 7+ years LVN and. 2 years CNA; a diverse nurse with many areas of expertise, a fast learner and strong leader who empowers performance with the flexibility to accommodate the ever changing demands in healthcare; desired outcomes seen through quality measures thus, striving for sustainability with continuous improvement and growth.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### Work Experience

#### LVN

Monarch Pavilion Rehabilitation Suites - Dallas, TX November 2017 to Present

Provide nursing care to residents as prescribed by the physician and in accordance with standards of nursing practices and regulations. Responsible for administration of treatments, medications, appointment scheduling, discharge, admission and re-admits assessments, follow up care, daily skilled nursing to enhance quality of life for residents, monitor intake and output levels, g-tubes, trach care etc; obtain vitals and glucose testing and provided pharmacy with prescription details to fill and refill orders, supervise nurses' aides or assistants and perform duties as required for the success of the team and to maintain resident satisfaction.

#### **Charge Nurse LVN**

Walnut Place - Dallas, TX November 2014 to July 2017

Provide nursing care to residents as prescribed by the physician and in accordance with standards of nursing practices and regulations. Responsible for administration of treatments, medications, appointment scheduling, discharge, admission and re-admits assessments, follow up care, daily skilled nursing to enhance quality of life for residents, monitor intake and output levels, g-tubes, trach care etc; obtain vitals and glucose testing and provided pharmacy with prescription details to fill and refill orders, supervise nurses' aides or assistants and perform duties as required for the success of the team and to maintain resident satisfaction.

#### **Charge Nurse LVN**

The Forum at Parklane - Dallas, TX May 2014 to October 2014

Provided nursing care to residents as prescribed by the physician and in accordance with standards of nursing practices and regulations. Responsible for administration of treatments, medications, appointment scheduling, discharge, admission and re-admits assessments, follow up care, daily skilled nursing to enhance quality of life for residents, monitor intake and output levels, g-tubes, trach care etc; obtain vitals and glucose testing and provided pharmacy with prescription details to fill and refill

orders, supervise nurses' aides or assistants and perform duties as required for the success of the team and to maintain resident satisfaction.

#### LVN

Williamsburg Village Healthcare Rehab - Dallas, TX April 2011 to May 2014

Provide nursing care to residents as prescribed by the physician and in accordance with standards of nursing practices and regulations. Responsible for administration of treatments, medications, appointment scheduling, discharge, admission and re-admits assessments, follow up care, daily skilled nursing to enhance quality of life for residents, monitor intake and output levels, g-tubes, trach care etc; obtain vitals and glucose testing and provided pharmacy with prescription details to fill and refill orders, supervise nurses' aides or assistants and perform duties as required for the success of the team and to maintain resident satisfaction.

## **Lead Customer Service Rep**

Comp Usa Corp - Dallas, TX August 1998 to April 2008

Resolved customer complaints and conveyed in a reassuring manner step by step instructions to resolve application issues.

## Education

Dallas Nursing Institute - Dallas, TX

## **Nursing Licenses**

#### PΝ

Expires: April 2018

State: TX

### Skills

Home Health, LVN

#### Certifications

## **IV Certification 2010**

May 2010 to Present

## **CPR/AED for Professional Rescuers and Health Care Providers**

October 2017 to October 2019